var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "لَإِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "(was) surely Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "la-ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "O Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yāib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَقَ",
        "answer": "he ran away",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "abaqa",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَآبَاؤُنَا",
        "answer": "Or our fathers",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "awaābāunā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their fathers",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "ābāahum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَائِكُمُ",
        "answer": "(of) your forefathers",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "ābāikumu",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَبِيهِ",
        "answer": "to his father",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "li-abīhi",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أَبَتِ",
        "answer": "O my father",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "yāabati",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتُونَنَا",
        "answer": "come (to) us",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "tatūnanā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتُوا",
        "answer": "Then bring",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "fatū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "And We gave both of them",
        "pcklId": "486",
        "tlit": "waātaynāhumā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "آثَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their footsteps",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "āthārihim",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the later generations",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the later generations",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the later generations",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the later generations",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخَرِينَ",
        "answer": "the others",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "l-ākharīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخَرِينَ",
        "answer": "the others",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "l-ākharīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Is it when",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "a-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "then, behold",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Is (it) when",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "a-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "But when",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "332",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِسْحَاقَ",
        "answer": "of Isaac",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "bi-is'ḥāqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْحَاقَ",
        "answer": "Isaac",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "is'ḥāqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) bottom",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "aṣli",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَئِفْكًا",
        "answer": "Is it falsehood ",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "a-if'kan",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِفْكِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their falsehood",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "if'kihim",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْكُلُونَ",
        "answer": "you eat",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "takulūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآكِلُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) surely eat",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "laākilūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْفٍ",
        "answer": "thousand",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "alfin",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "426",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "427",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "428",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "429",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "430",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "431",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "432",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "433",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "434",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "435",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "436",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "437",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "1048",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1049",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلِيمِ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-alīmi",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "ilāhakum",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَتِنَا",
        "answer": "our gods",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "ālihatinā",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةً",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "ālihatan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their gods",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "ālihatihim",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2246",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2247",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2248",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "By Allah",
        "pcklId": "2249",
        "tlit": "tal-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2250",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah ",
        "pcklId": "2251",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "While Allah",
        "pcklId": "2252",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah wills",
        "pcklId": "2253",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2254",
        "tlit": "al-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2255",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has begotten",
        "pcklId": "2256",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2257",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2258",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2259",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(be) to Allah",
        "pcklId": "2260",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "554",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "555",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَإِلَى",
        "answer": "(will) surely be to",
        "pcklId": "556",
        "tlit": "la-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "557",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "towards him",
        "pcklId": "558",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "559",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "560",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "until",
        "pcklId": "561",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "562",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "563",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلْيَاسَ",
        "answer": "Elijah",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "il'yāsa",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلْ يَاسِينَ",
        "answer": "Elijah",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "il yāsīna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْمَرُ",
        "answer": "you are commanded",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "tu'maru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآمَنُوا",
        "answer": "And they believed",
        "pcklId": "428",
        "tlit": "faāmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "810",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believing",
        "pcklId": "811",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believing",
        "pcklId": "847",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believing",
        "pcklId": "848",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believing",
        "pcklId": "849",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِنَاثًا",
        "answer": "females",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ināthan",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلَهُ",
        "answer": "and his family",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlahu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلَهُ",
        "answer": "and his family",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlahu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُولَىٰ",
        "answer": "the first",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-ūlā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "the former (people)",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلُونَ",
        "answer": "former",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-awalūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the former (people)",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) your forefathers",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "a Sign",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَارَكْنَا",
        "answer": "And We blessed",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wabāraknā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَشَّرْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "So We gave him the glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "fabasharnāhu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَشَّرْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We gave him glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wabasharnāhu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْصِرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "And see them",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wa-abṣir'hum",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they will see",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْصِرْ",
        "answer": "And see",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "wa-abṣir",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they will see",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبُطُونَ",
        "answer": "(their) bellies",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-buṭūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَطْنِهِ",
        "answer": "its belly",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "baṭnihi",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْعَثُونَ",
        "answer": "they are resurrected",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yub'ʿathūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَبْعُوثُونَ",
        "answer": "be certainly resurrected",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "lamabʿūthūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "others",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُهُمْ",
        "answer": "some of them",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "baʿḍuhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "others",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "baʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْلًا",
        "answer": "Baal",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baʿlan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَاقِينَ",
        "answer": "the survivors",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-bāqīna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَغَ",
        "answer": "he reached",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "balagha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَلَاءُ",
        "answer": "the trial",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-balāu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنُوا",
        "answer": "Build",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ib'nū",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَنَاتُ",
        "answer": "(have) daughters",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-banātu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَنَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] daughters",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-banāti",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بُنَيَّ",
        "answer": "O my son",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "yābunayya",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَنُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) sons",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "l-banūna",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَنِينَ",
        "answer": "sons",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "l-banīna",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُنْيَانًا",
        "answer": "a structure",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "bun'yānan",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْضَاءَ",
        "answer": "White",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bayḍāa",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْضٌ",
        "answer": "eggs",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "bayḍun",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمَا",
        "answer": "(is) between both of them",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "baynahumā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُ",
        "answer": "between Him",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "baynahu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَ",
        "answer": "and between",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "wabayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "452",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبِينُ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "453",
        "tlit": "l-mubīnu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "454",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "510",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْتَبِينَ",
        "answer": "the clear",
        "pcklId": "522",
        "tlit": "l-mus'tabīna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَتْبَعَهُ",
        "answer": "but follows him",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "fa-atbaʿahu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرَابًا",
        "answer": "dust",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "turāban",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرَابًا",
        "answer": "dust",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "turāban",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَكْنَا",
        "answer": "And We left",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wataraknā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَكْنَا",
        "answer": "And We left",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wataraknā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَكْنَا",
        "answer": "And We left",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wataraknā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَكْنَا",
        "answer": "And We left",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wataraknā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَارِكُو",
        "answer": "to leave",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "latārikū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَلَّهُ",
        "answer": "and he put him down",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "watallahu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالتَّالِيَاتِ",
        "answer": "And those who recite",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "fal-tāliyāti",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَاقِبٌ",
        "answer": "piercing",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "thāqibun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْجَبِينِ",
        "answer": "upon his forehead",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lil'jabīni",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "the blazing Fire",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمِ",
        "answer": "(in) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīmi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "with the criminals",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "bil-muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُجْزَوْنَ",
        "answer": "you will be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "tuj'zawna",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "[We] reward",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "[We] reward",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "We reward",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "reward",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "reward",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "[We] have made it",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnāhā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We made",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "but We made them",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "fajaʿalnāhumu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلُوا",
        "answer": "And they have made",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalū",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْمَعِينَ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ajmaʿīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَانِبٍ",
        "answer": "side",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "jānibin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنْدَنَا",
        "answer": "Our host",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "jundanā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنَّةِ",
        "answer": "the jinn",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-jinati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنَّةُ",
        "answer": "the jinn",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-jinatu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتِ",
        "answer": "Gardens",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "jannāti",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَجْنُونٍ",
        "answer": "mad",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "majnūnin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُجِيبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are We as) Responders",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-mujībūna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "he has brought",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "he came",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنَ",
        "answer": "(the) Best",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "aḥsana",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحْسِنٌ",
        "answer": "(are) good-doers",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "muḥ'sinun",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "احْشُرُوا",
        "answer": "Gather",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "uḥ'shurū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْضَرِينَ",
        "answer": "those brought",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'ḍarīna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُحْضَرُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) surely be brought",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "lamuḥ'ḍarūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُحْضَرُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) surely be brought",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "lamuḥ'ḍarūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحِفْظًا",
        "answer": "And (to) guard",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "waḥif'ẓan",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَحَقَّ",
        "answer": "So has been proved true",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "faḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْكُمُونَ",
        "answer": "you judge",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "taḥkumūna",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "forbearing",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ḥalīmin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "And all praise",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wal-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمِيمٍ",
        "answer": "boiling water",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥamīmin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُوتُ",
        "answer": "the fish",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ḥūtu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينٍ",
        "answer": "a while",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ḥīnin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينٍ",
        "answer": "a time",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ḥīnin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينٍ",
        "answer": "a time",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ḥīnin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْرُجُ",
        "answer": "that grows",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "takhruju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَطِفَ",
        "answer": "snatches",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khaṭifa",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَطْفَةَ",
        "answer": "(by) theft",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-khaṭfata",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُخْلَصِينَ",
        "answer": "the chosen ones",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-mukh'laṣīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُخْلَصِينَ",
        "answer": "the chosen ones",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-mukh'laṣīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُخْلَصِينَ",
        "answer": "the chosen ones",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-mukh'laṣīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُخْلَصِينَ",
        "answer": "the chosen",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-mukh'laṣīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُخْلَصِينَ",
        "answer": "the chosen",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-mukh'laṣīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We have created",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "khalaqnā",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "created them",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "khalaqnāhum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "created you",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "khalaqakum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَا",
        "answer": "did We create",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "khalaqnā",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقًا",
        "answer": "creation",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "khalqan",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَالِقِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) Creators ",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "l-khāliqīna",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "better",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدْبِرِينَ",
        "answer": "departing",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "mud'birīna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُحُورًا",
        "answer": "Repelled",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "duḥūran",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُدْحَضِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-mud'ḥaḍīna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَاخِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) humiliated",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "dākhirūna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "Do you call",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "atadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَمَّرْنَا",
        "answer": "We destroyed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "dammarnā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "[the world]",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "Besides",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونَ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "dūna",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Recompense",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَدِينُونَ",
        "answer": "surely be brought to Judgment",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "lamadīnūna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَذْبَحُكَ",
        "answer": "sacrificing you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "adhbaḥuka",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذِبْحٍ",
        "answer": "with a sacrifice",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "bidhib'ḥin",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتَهُ",
        "answer": "his offspring",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatahu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتِهِمَا",
        "answer": "their offspring",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatihimā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they receive admonition",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "yadhkurūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِّرُوا",
        "answer": "they are reminded",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "dhukkirū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "you pay heed",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "tadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرًا",
        "answer": "(the) Message",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "dhik'ran",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرًا",
        "answer": "a reminder",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "dhik'ran",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَاهِبٌ",
        "answer": "going",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "dhāhibun",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَذَائِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) certainly taste",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ladhāiqūna",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَذَائِقُو",
        "answer": "(will) surely taste",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ladhāiqū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُءُوسُ",
        "answer": "(was) heads",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ruūsu",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "ra-aw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَآهُ",
        "answer": "and see him",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "faraāhu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "have seen",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "arā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّؤْيَا",
        "answer": "the vision",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "l-ru'yā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "Lord",
        "pcklId": "680",
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبُّ",
        "answer": "and Lord",
        "pcklId": "681",
        "tlit": "warabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "(of) our Lord",
        "pcklId": "682",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(of) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "683",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "(to) his Lord",
        "pcklId": "684",
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّ",
        "answer": "about (the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "685",
        "tlit": "birabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "686",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "687",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "688",
        "tlit": "rabbakum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبَّ",
        "answer": "and (the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "689",
        "tlit": "warabba",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِرَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "Does your Lord",
        "pcklId": "690",
        "tlit": "alirabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(be to) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "691",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "692",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "693",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْجِعَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their return",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "marjiʿahum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتُرْدِينِ",
        "answer": "ruined me",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "latur'dīni",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) a provision",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "riz'qun",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْسَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We sent him",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "wa-arsalnāhu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "505",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "506",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "507",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "508",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "509",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "511",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "(that) you desire",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "turīdūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَرَادُوا",
        "answer": "And they intended",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "fa-arādū",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَاغَ",
        "answer": "Then he turned",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "farāgha",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَاغَ",
        "answer": "Then he turned",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "farāgha",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَجْرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) a cry",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "zajratun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَجْرًا",
        "answer": "strongly",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "zajran",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالزَّاجِرَاتِ",
        "answer": "And those who drive",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fal-zājirāti",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزِفُّونَ",
        "answer": "hastening",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaziffūna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّقُّومِ",
        "answer": "(of) Zaqqum",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-zaqūmi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَزْوَاجَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their kinds",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "wa-azwājahum",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَزِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "more",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yazīdūna",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَيَّنَّا",
        "answer": "[We] adorned",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "zayyannā",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِزِينَةٍ",
        "answer": "with an adornment",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "bizīnatin",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَسَاءَلُونَ",
        "answer": "questioning one another",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "yatasāalūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَسَاءَلُونَ",
        "answer": "questioning one another",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "yatasāalūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْئُولُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) to be questioned",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "masūlūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "Glory be",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "Glory",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسَبِّحِينَ",
        "answer": "those who glorify",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-musabiḥīna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسَبِّحُونَ",
        "answer": "glorify (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-musabiḥūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَقَتْ",
        "answer": "has preceded",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "sabaqat",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِحْرٌ",
        "answer": "a magic",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "siḥ'run",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْخَرُونَ",
        "answer": "while they mock",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wayaskharūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَسْخِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they mock",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "yastaskhirūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُرُرٍ",
        "answer": "thrones",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "sururin",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّعْيَ",
        "answer": "the (age of) working with him",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-saʿya",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْفَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the lowest",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-asfalīna",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَقِيمٌ",
        "answer": "sick",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "saqīmun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَقِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(was) ill",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "saqīmun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانٍ",
        "answer": "authority",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭānin",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانٌ",
        "answer": "an authority",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭānun",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْلَمَا",
        "answer": "both of them had submitted",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "aslamā",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Peace be",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "salāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Peace be",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "salāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Peace be",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "salāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Peace be",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "salāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "And peace be",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wasalāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "sound",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "salīmin",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَسْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) surrender",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "mus'taslimūna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسَّمَّعُونَ",
        "answer": "they may listen",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "yassammaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "l-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَاهَمَ",
        "answer": "Then he drew lots",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fasāhama",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَاءَ",
        "answer": "then evil (will be)",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "fasāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسَاحَتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "in their territory",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bisāḥatihim",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءِ",
        "answer": "(the) midst",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "sawāi",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَجَرَةُ",
        "answer": "(the) tree",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "shajaratu",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَجَرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a tree",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "shajaratun",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَجَرَةً",
        "answer": "a plant",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "shajaratan",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْحُونِ",
        "answer": "laden",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-mashḥūni",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "a stronger",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلشَّارِبِينَ",
        "answer": "for the drinkers",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "lilshāribīna",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشَارِقِ",
        "answer": "(of) each point of sunrise",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-mashāriqi",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُشْتَرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) sharers",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "mush'tarikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيَاطِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the devils",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-shayāṭīni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْطَانٍ",
        "answer": "devil",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "shayṭānin",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِشَاعِرٍ",
        "answer": "for a poet",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "lishāʿirin",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِهَابٌ",
        "answer": "a burning flame",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shihābun",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاهِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) witnesses",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "shāhidūna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَشَوْبًا",
        "answer": "(is) a mixture",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lashawban",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "Allah wills",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِيعَتِهِ",
        "answer": "his kind",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "shīʿatihi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَاحُ",
        "answer": "(the) morning",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ṣabāḥu",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصْبِحِينَ",
        "answer": "(in the) morning",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "muṣ'biḥīna",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the patient ones",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "l-ṣābirīna",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَدَّقَ",
        "answer": "and confirmed",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "waṣaddaqa",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَّقْتَ",
        "answer": "you have fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ṣaddaqta",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُصَدِّقِينَ",
        "answer": "those who believe",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "l-muṣadiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطِ",
        "answer": "(the) Path",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭi",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصِّرَاطَ",
        "answer": "(to) the Path",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-ṣirāṭa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَفًّا",
        "answer": "(in) rows",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ṣaffan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصَّافَّاتِ",
        "answer": "By those lined",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wal-ṣāfāti",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّافُّونَ",
        "answer": "stand in rows",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāfūna",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْطَفَى",
        "answer": "Has He chosen",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "aṣṭafā",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِ",
        "answer": "(is) to burn",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ṣāli",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرْبًا",
        "answer": "striking",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ḍarban",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَّ",
        "answer": "went astray",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَالِّينَ",
        "answer": "astray",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "ḍāllīna",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّرْفِ",
        "answer": "(will be) companions of modest gaze",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-ṭarfi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَاغِينَ",
        "answer": "transgressing",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ṭāghīna",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاطَّلَعَ",
        "answer": "Then he (will) look",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fa-iṭṭalaʿa",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَلْعُهَا",
        "answer": "Its emerging fruit",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ṭalʿuhā",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُطَّلِعُونَ",
        "answer": "be looking",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "muṭṭaliʿūna",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُطَافُ",
        "answer": "Will be circulated",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuṭāfu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "طِينٍ",
        "answer": "a clay",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ṭīnin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "wronged",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "lilẓẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَالِمٌ",
        "answer": "and unjust",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "waẓālimun",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "(do) you think",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ẓannukum",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "worship",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "yaʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "you worship",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "Do you worship",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "ataʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "you worship",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادَ",
        "answer": "(the) slaves",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "ʿibāda",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادَ",
        "answer": "(the) slaves",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "ʿibāda",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِنَا",
        "answer": "Our slaves",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "ʿibādinā",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِنَا",
        "answer": "Our slaves",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "ʿibādinā",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِنَا",
        "answer": "Our slaves",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "ʿibādinā",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادَ",
        "answer": "(the) slaves",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "ʿibāda",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِنَا",
        "answer": "Our slaves",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "ʿibādinā",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادَ",
        "answer": "(the) slaves",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "ʿibāda",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادَ",
        "answer": "slaves",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "ʿibāda",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِعِبَادِنَا",
        "answer": "for Our slaves",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "liʿibādinā",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَجِبْتَ",
        "answer": "you wonder",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ʿajib'ta",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَجُوزًا",
        "answer": "an old woman",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ʿajūzan",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَعْجِلُونَ",
        "answer": "they hasten",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yastaʿjilūna",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَبِعَذَابِنَا",
        "answer": "Then is (it) for Our punishment",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "afabiʿadhābinā",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمُعَذَّبِينَ",
        "answer": "will be punished",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "tlit": "bimuʿadhabīna",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعَرَاءِ",
        "answer": "onto the open shore",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿarāi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِزَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Honor",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "l-ʿizati",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٍ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِظَامًا",
        "answer": "and bones",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "waʿiẓāman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِظَامًا",
        "answer": "and bones",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "waʿiẓāman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "(the) end",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "you use reason",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمَتِ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "ʿalimati",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "they will know",
        "pcklId": "298",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "529",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "530",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "531",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْلُومٌ",
        "answer": "determined",
        "pcklId": "847",
        "tlit": "maʿlūmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْلُومٌ",
        "answer": "known",
        "pcklId": "848",
        "tlit": "maʿlūmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "[the] exalted",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-aʿlā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَعْمَلِ",
        "answer": "let work",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "falyaʿmali",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you make",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَامِلُونَ",
        "answer": "the workers",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "l-ʿāmilūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِنْدَهُمْ",
        "answer": "And with them",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "waʿindahum",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَنَا",
        "answer": "we had",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "ʿindanā",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِينٌ",
        "answer": "(having) beautiful eyes",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ʿīnun",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعِينٍ",
        "answer": "a flowing spring",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "maʿīnin",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "those who remained behind",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-ghābirīna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْرَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We drowned",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "aghraqnā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَالِبِينَ",
        "answer": "the victors",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-ghālibīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَالِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) those who overcome",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-ghālibūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغُلَامٍ",
        "answer": "of a boy",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bighulāmin",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَوْلٌ",
        "answer": "(is) bad effect",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ghawlun",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَغْوَيْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "So we led you astray",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fa-aghwaynākum",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَاوِينَ",
        "answer": "astray",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ghāwīna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةً",
        "answer": "a trial",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "fit'natan",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِفَاتِنِينَ",
        "answer": "can tempt away (anyone)",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "bifātinīna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَفْتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "Then ask them",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taftihim",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَفْتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "Then ask them",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taftihim",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَدَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We ransomed him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wafadaynāhu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَصْلِ",
        "answer": "(of) Judgment",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-faṣli",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْعَلُ",
        "answer": "We deal",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "nafʿalu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْعَلْ",
        "answer": "Do",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "if'ʿal",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَاكِهُ",
        "answer": "Fruits",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fawākihu",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفُلْكِ",
        "answer": "the ship",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-ful'ki",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوْزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the attainment",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-fawzu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقْبَلَ",
        "answer": "And will approach",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wa-aqbala",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَقْبَلَ",
        "answer": "And (will) approach",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "fa-aqbala",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَقْبَلُوا",
        "answer": "Then they advanced",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fa-aqbalū",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "qablahum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَقَابِلِينَ",
        "answer": "facing each other",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "mutaqābilīna",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُقْذَفُونَ",
        "answer": "are pelted",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wayuq'dhafūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِينٌ",
        "answer": "a companion",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "qarīnun",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاصِرَاتُ",
        "answer": "(will be) companions of modest gaze",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "qāṣirātu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَلْبٍ",
        "answer": "with a heart",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "biqalbin",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "1300",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1301",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they will say",
        "pcklId": "1302",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They will say",
        "pcklId": "1303",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They will say",
        "pcklId": "1304",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it was said",
        "pcklId": "1305",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "1306",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Will say",
        "pcklId": "1307",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "Who (would) say",
        "pcklId": "1308",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He (will) say",
        "pcklId": "1309",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He (will) say",
        "pcklId": "1310",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "1311",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And he said",
        "pcklId": "1312",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and said",
        "pcklId": "1313",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1314",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "1315",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And he said",
        "pcklId": "1316",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "1317",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1318",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "1319",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "[they] say",
        "pcklId": "1320",
        "tlit": "layaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "1321",
        "tlit": "layaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلُ",
        "answer": "(the) Word",
        "pcklId": "1693",
        "tlit": "qawlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَائِلٌ",
        "answer": "a speaker",
        "pcklId": "1721",
        "tlit": "qāilun",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "and his people",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "waqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَوْمَهُمَا",
        "answer": "and their people",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "waqawmahumā",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "to his people",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقَامٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a position",
        "pcklId": "578",
        "tlit": "maqāmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْتَقِيمَ",
        "answer": "the Straight",
        "pcklId": "658",
        "tlit": "l-mus'taqīma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكَأْسٍ",
        "answer": "a cup",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bikasin",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَكْبِرُونَ",
        "answer": "were arrogant",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yastakbirūna",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكِتَابِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your book",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "bikitābikum",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرُ",
        "answer": "most",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "aktharu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "answer": "deny",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "tukadhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَذَّبُوهُ",
        "answer": "But they denied him",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "fakadhabūhu",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكَاذِبُونَ",
        "answer": "surely (are) liars",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "lakādhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَرْبِ",
        "answer": "the distress",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-karbi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَرْبِ",
        "answer": "the distress",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-karbi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُكْرَمُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) be honored",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "muk'ramūna",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "But they disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "fakafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَتُنَا",
        "answer": "Our Word",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "kalimatunā",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكْنُونٌ",
        "answer": "well protected",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "maknūnun",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِدْتَ",
        "answer": "you almost",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "kidtta",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَوَاكِبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the stars",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-kawākibi",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "and have become",
        "pcklId": "1068",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "1069",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used (to)",
        "pcklId": "1070",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "[you] used (to)",
        "pcklId": "1071",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "1072",
        "tlit": "takūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "1073",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "1074",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "1075",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "1076",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "1077",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "had",
        "pcklId": "1078",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "and become",
        "pcklId": "1079",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكُنْتُ",
        "answer": "certainly, I (would) have been",
        "pcklId": "1080",
        "tlit": "lakuntu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "1081",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "so they became",
        "pcklId": "1082",
        "tlit": "fakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and was",
        "pcklId": "1083",
        "tlit": "fakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "1084",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "1085",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1086",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "Certainly, we (would) have been",
        "pcklId": "1087",
        "tlit": "lakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدًا",
        "answer": "a plot",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "kaydan",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "How",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَلَبِثَ",
        "answer": "Certainly, he (would have) remained",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "lalabitha",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَذَّةٍ",
        "answer": "delicious",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ladhatin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَازِبٍ",
        "answer": "sticky",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lāzibin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْفَوْا",
        "answer": "found",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "alfaw",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالْتَقَمَهُ",
        "answer": "Then swallowed him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fal-taqamahu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَلْقُوهُ",
        "answer": "and throw him",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "fa-alqūhu",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(was) blameworthy",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "mulīmun",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "And at night",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "wabi-al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِائَةِ",
        "answer": "a hundred",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "mi-ati",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَتَّعْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "so We gave them enjoyment",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "famattaʿnāhum",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِمِثْلِ",
        "answer": "For (the) like",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "limith'li",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَارِدٍ",
        "answer": "rebellious",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "māridin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَمُرُّونَ",
        "answer": "surely pass",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "latamurrūna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَإِ",
        "answer": "the assembly",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-mala-i",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَالِئُونَ",
        "answer": "and fill",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "famāliūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةَ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "l-malāikata",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَنَّا",
        "answer": "We conferred Favor",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "manannā",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِتْنَا",
        "answer": "we are dead",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "mit'nā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِتْنَا",
        "answer": "we have died",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "mit'nā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْتَتَنَا",
        "answer": "our death",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "mawtatanā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَيِّتِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) die",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "bimayyitīna",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبِيًّا",
        "answer": "a Prophet",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "nabiyyan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْبَتْنَا",
        "answer": "And We caused to grow",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wa-anbatnā",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَبَذْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "But We cast him",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fanabadhnāhu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّجُومِ",
        "answer": "the stars",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-nujūmi",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجَّيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We saved him",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wanajjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجَّيْنَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "And We saved both of them",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wanajjaynāhumā",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجَّيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We saved him",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "najjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْحِتُونَ",
        "answer": "you carve",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tanḥitūna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَادَانَا",
        "answer": "called Us",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "nādānā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَادَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We called out to him",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wanādaynāhu",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْذِرِينَ",
        "answer": "warners",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "mundhirīna",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْذَرِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who were warned",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "l-mundharīna",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْذَرِينَ",
        "answer": "(for) those who were warned",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "l-mundharīna",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْزَفُونَ",
        "answer": "will be intoxicated",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yunzafūna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَلَ",
        "answer": "it descends",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nazala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُزُلًا",
        "answer": "(as) hospitality",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "nuzulan",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسَبًا",
        "answer": "a relationship",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nasaban",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَصَرْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We helped them",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "wanaṣarnāhum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنَاصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "you help one another",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "tanāṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَنْصُورُونَ",
        "answer": "(would be) the victorious",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "l-manṣūrūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْطِقُونَ",
        "answer": "you speak",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tanṭiqūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "will see",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْظُرْ",
        "answer": "Then see",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "fa-unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَظَرَ",
        "answer": "Then he glanced",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "fanaẓara",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْظُرْ",
        "answer": "so look",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "fa-unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَظْرَةً",
        "answer": "a glance",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "naẓratan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَنِعْمَ",
        "answer": "and Best",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "falaniʿ'ma",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَةُ",
        "answer": "(for the) Grace",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matu",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّعِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) Delight",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "l-naʿīmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "to himself",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "linafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَنَامِ",
        "answer": "the dream",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-manāmi",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاهْدُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "then lead them",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "fa-ih'dūhum",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَهْدِينِ",
        "answer": "He will guide me",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "sayahdīni",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهَدَيْنَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "And We guided both of them",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "wahadaynāhumā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُهْرَعُونَ",
        "answer": "they hastened",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuh'raʿūna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَتَجِدُنِي",
        "answer": "You will find me",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "satajidunī",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَوَاحِدٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely One",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "lawāḥidun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةٌ",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَذَرُونَ",
        "answer": "and you forsake",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "watadharūna",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاصِبٌ",
        "answer": "perpetual",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wāṣibun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصِفُونَ",
        "answer": "they attribute",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yaṣifūna",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصِفُونَ",
        "answer": "they attribute",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yaṣifūna",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِفُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "And stop them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waqifūhum",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "you fear",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "tattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَدَ",
        "answer": "Allah has begotten",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "walada",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "So they turned away",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "fatawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَوَلَّ",
        "answer": "So turn away",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "fatawalla",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَوَلَّ",
        "answer": "So turn away",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "watawalla",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَبْ",
        "answer": "grant",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "hab",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِينِ",
        "answer": "the right",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-yamīni",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْيَمِينِ",
        "answer": "with the right hand",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "bil-yamīni",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Day",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "yawmu",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Day",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "yawmu",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on) that Day",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the Day",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "37",
        "ayah": "144"
    }
]; 
export default words;